What name is given to this one?
A hen.
A hen, very good.
Now, if this is a hen we looked at this is a what?
A mouth.
Kasamba, you can see what about this side?
Aha.
What is that?
Beak
Beak? Aha. Then there?
This is head.
Head. Then?
And ...
It has also a neck.
My school is Bishop Willis Demonstration School which is an inclusive school.
It is inclusive in a way that has the normal children and the special needs education children.
We include them in the normal classes so at least they should not feel isolated.
They are also human beings like the others.
When it once comes for trying for braille, they have their resource room.
They come to the braille room and the specialist in specialist needs
train them in  how to read and how to write using the braille machine.
And they have about five teachers who are specialists
who handle these visually impaired children.